{
    "subject": "resource/Lottie_Williams",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Indiana",
    "human_readable": "Lottie Williams was born in Indiana.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9240414500236511,
            "question": "Where was Lottie Williams born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7932918667793274,
            "question": "What year was Lottie Williams born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6526419520378113,
            "question": "Is there a historical significance to Lottie Williams' birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44186466932296753,
            "question": "Does Lottie Williams have any notable relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18739497661590576,
            "question": "What state is Indiana known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12746025621891022,
            "question": "Can you name any famous people from Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09492243826389313,
            "question": "What are some famous landmarks in Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07522190362215042,
            "question": "What are some popular attractions in Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0585329644382,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05811355635523796,
            "question": "What is the capital city of Indiana?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lottie Williams was born in Indiana.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3478_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Indiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3478_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular attractions in Indiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3478_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some famous landmarks in Indiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3478_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3478_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Lottie Williams was born in Indiana\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3478/re-ranker-msmarco/44.txt) states that Lottie Williams was born in Indianapolis, Indiana, USA. Another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3478/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt) also mentions that she was born in 1874 in Indianapolis, Indiana, USA. Therefore, the information supports the triple \"Lottie Williams was born in Indiana\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Lottie Williams was born in Indiana.\" Specifically, multiple files mention her birthplace as Indianapolis, Indiana, USA."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}